(Howard:)Anyway, sir,
l need to talk to you about something.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)Walnut?
(Howard:)No, thank you. I'm allergic.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)Oh, sure. My partner used to have that.
He's dead now.
- From nuts, heh?
- No, his wife shot him.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)But she was nuts. So in a way...
(Howard:)Nice story. Anyway...
(Howard:)...the reason
l wanted to talk to you is...
(Howard:)...NASA has moved up my launch
to the lnternational Space Station.
- Yeah, so?
- So the date is going to conflict...
(Howard:)...with me marrying your daughter.
Now, I know what you're going to say.
l made a commitment to Bernadette
and to your family...
...and l've got a lot of nerve coming here
and demanding that we postpone this.
(Howard:)Well, message heard and understood.
Mission cancelled. Thank you.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)Where are you going?
(Leonard:)I'm sorry.
(Howard:)May I be excused?